Save your family or save humanity. Make the choice.
Knock at the Cabin is a horror, mystery, thriller
film directed by M. Night Shyamalan.
While vacationing at a remote cabin, a young girl and her two fathers are taken hostage by four armed
strangers who demand that the family make an unthinkable choice to avert the apocalypse.
With limited access to the outside world, the family must
decide what they believe before all is lost.
Leonard, played by Dave Bautista.
Eric, played by Jonathan Groff.
Andrew, played by Ben Aldridge.
Sabrina, played by Nikki Amuka-Bird.
Redmond, played by Rupert Grint.
Adriane, played by Abby Quinn.
Knock at the Cabin is a 2023 American apocalyptic psychological
horror film co-written, directed and produced by M.
Night Shyamalan, who wrote the screenplay from an initial
draft by Steve Desmond and Michael Sherman.
It is based on the 2018 novel The Cabin at the End of the World by Paul G.
Tremblay, the first adaptation of one of his works.
The film stars Dave Bautista, Jonathan Groff, Ben Aldridge, Nikki
Amuka-Bird, Kristen Cui, Abby Quinn, and Rupert Grint.
In the film, a family is vacationing at a remote cabin when they are suddenly held
hostage by four strangers who ask them to do something unimaginable.
Knock at the Cabin premiered in New York City at the Rose Hall on January 30, 2023, and was
theatrically released in the United States on February 3, 2023, by Universal Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed over $54 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
sacrifice, faith, end of the world, apocalypse.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.